<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Family Recipes</title><link>https://poegel.kitchen/</link><description>Recent content on Family Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 15:04:49 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://poegel.kitchen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Friday Night Pizza</title><link>https://poegel.kitchen/recipe/friday-night-pizza/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 15:04:49 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://poegel.kitchen/recipe/friday-night-pizza/</guid><description>Wednesday Night In a small bowl combine the starter, whole wheat flour, 100g AP flour, and 100g warm water. Cover and let sit at room temperature overnight. Thursday Night In a medium bowl combine 450g AP flour and 310g warm water. Cover and let rest for 30 minutes. Add about 90g levain that was created the night before and salt. Cover and let rest for 30 minutes. Wet hands with water and briefly knead and then rest for 30 minutes twice more.</description></item><item><title>Chocolate Chip Cookies</title><link>https://poegel.kitchen/recipe/chocolate-chip-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 15:04:31 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://poegel.kitchen/recipe/chocolate-chip-cookies/</guid><description> Preheat oven to 350. Cream together the butter, white sugar, and brown sugar until smooth. Beat in the eggs one at a time, then stir in the vanilla. Dissolve baking soda in hot water. Add to batter along with salt. Stir in flour and then add chocolate chips. Drop by large spoonfuls onto parchment paper-lined cookie sheet. Bake for about 10 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Is this Pad Thai? No This is Patrick</title><link>https://poegel.kitchen/recipe/pad-thai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 20:09:30 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://poegel.kitchen/recipe/pad-thai/</guid><description>Mix the lime juice, brown sugar, soy sauce, white wine vinegar, sriracha sauce, and cayenne pepper in a small bowl and set aside. Cook the rice noodles as per instructions on the box. Saute the chicken until browned with salt and pepper. Add the garlic. Push the chicken to the side of the pan. Saute the red pepper and the chili pepper. Push the chicken and peppers to the side and add the egg.</description></item><item><title>Pineapple Orange Punch</title><link>https://poegel.kitchen/recipe/pineapple-orange-punch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 21:05:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://poegel.kitchen/recipe/pineapple-orange-punch/</guid><description> Add pineapple juice, light rum, dark rum, and orange juice to a shaker and shake to combine. Pour into a collins glass and top with sprite. Optionally, add a pineapple slice to the rim for garnish.</description></item><item><title>Margarita</title><link>https://poegel.kitchen/recipe/margarita/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 21:05:34 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://poegel.kitchen/recipe/margarita/</guid><description>Combine lime juice, orange liquor, tequila, salt, and sugar in a shaker with an ice cube and shake vigorously until the ice cube has melted. Pour into a tumbler glass filled with ice. Pour splash of fruited liquor over the top. This recipe also works with mezcal instead of tequila.</description></item><item><title>Fish Tacos</title><link>https://poegel.kitchen/recipe/fish-tacos/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 20:57:14 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://poegel.kitchen/recipe/fish-tacos/</guid><description>Prep the fish by rinsing and patting dry. In a small bowl, stir fish rub spices together. Sprinkle all sides of fish lightly with the spice rub. Set aside. Make the slaw by placing the shredded cabbage in a medium bowl. Toss with the salt. Add the onions, cilantro, jalapeño, lime juice, olive oil and toss well. Grease the grill well before placing fish on it. Turn heat to medium.</description></item><item><title>Molasses Cookies</title><link>https://poegel.kitchen/recipe/molasses-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 20:21:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://poegel.kitchen/recipe/molasses-cookies/</guid><description>In a medium bowl, whisk together flour, soda, cinnamon, cloves, ginger and salt. Set aside. Using a separate mixing bowl, either with a stand mixer or a hand mixer, cream together the softened butter and sugars on medium-high speed until the mixture is light and fluffy and a pale yellow color, about 2 minutes, scraping down the sides occasionally as needed. Mix in the eggs (one at a time) and molasses, and beat on medium-low speed until each is combined.</description></item></channel></rss>